{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-11",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 11",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "english-5",
    "unit11",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 11: Family time",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "beach",
      "answer": "bãi biển",
      "speak": "beach"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "collect",
      "answer": "thu thập, sưu tầm",
      "speak": "collect"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "seashell",
      "answer": "vỏ sò",
      "speak": "seashell"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "summer",
      "answer": "mùa hè",
      "speak": "summer"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "bay",
      "answer": "vịnh",
      "speak": "bay"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "postcard",
      "answer": "bưu thiếp",
      "speak": "postcard"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "boat trip",
      "answer": "chuyến du thuyền",
      "speak": "boat trip"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "seafood",
      "answer": "hải sản",
      "speak": "seafood"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "souvenir",
      "answer": "quà lưu niệm",
      "speak": "souvenir"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "stay",
      "answer": "ở lại",
      "speak": "stay"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "hotel",
      "answer": "khách sạn",
      "speak": "hotel"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "sunbath",
      "answer": "tắm nắng",
      "speak": "sunbath"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "explore",
      "answer": "khám phá",
      "speak": "explore"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "journey",
      "answer": "chuyến đi",
      "speak": "journey"
    }
  ]
}